Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art public relations and graphics records circa 1942-2009 COR0003.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibition files, 1944-2009; 1983-2009; Series 11
  - FY 88 Simonds Dwelling (recto), 1987-1988; Series 11 (Box 69, Folder 51)
  - FY 88 Simonds Smear I, 1987-1988; Series 11 (Box 69, Folder 52)
  - FY 88 Simonds Red Flower, 1987-1988; Series 11 (Box 69, Folder 53)
  - FY 88 Simonds Refuge, 1987-1988; Series 11 (Box 69, Folder 54)
  - Copley Head of a Negro 1777-1778, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Mount, Farmers Nooning, 1836, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Copley, Watson The Shark, 1778, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Marsh, Tuesday Night at the Savoy Ballroom, 1930, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Shaker Exhibition Slides and Transparencies, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Terra Sancta - Frank DiPerna Blue Mesa, Petrified Forest, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Terra Sancta - Peter von zur Muehlen Ringg Road, Kathmandu, Nepal, 1984, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Terra Sancta - Bernis von zur Muehlen, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Arnold Kramer, Sinai, 1985, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - 10+10 - Donald Sultan Gladiolas in a Chinese Pot, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - 10+10 - Vladimir Mironeko Stable Mutual Aid, 1988, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - 10+10 - Yuri Albert I'm Not Baselitz, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - 10+10 - Master set of glossies, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - 10+10 - Aleksei Sundukov Face to Face, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Peter Halley Christoper Brown, 1987 - 1989; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - David Bates, 1988; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Mark Tansey, 1986; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Greg Hannan Russian Garden 1990, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Greg Hannan Trenody 1987, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Greg Hannan: Irish Flag, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Sabina Ott Portrait Nacissus II, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Sabina Ott Disappearance Return #10, 1989; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Sabina Ott Disappearance Return #9, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Susan Hauptman: Negatives, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Susan Hauptman: Self Portrait '84, 1984; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Susan Hauptman: Still Life '85, 1985; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Susan Hauptman: Still Life '86, 1986; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Susan Hauptman: Self Portrait '89 SU, 1989; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Original Glossies, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Lee Friedlander, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Lee Friedlander - Rome, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Lee Friedlander - New York City, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Lee Friedlander - Woodman, Wisconsin, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Lee Friedlander - Canyon De Chelly, Arizona, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Lee Friedlander - Pittsburgh, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Winslow Homer, Kissing the Moon 1904, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Winslow Homer, Northeaster, 1895, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Winslow Homer, Light on the Sea, 1897, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Winslow Homer, Right and Left, 1909, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Winslow Homer, Early Morning.., 1902, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Winslow Homer, Winter Coast, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 41)
  - George Bellows, The Sea, 1911, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 42)
  - Rockwell Kent, Maine Coast, 1907, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 43)
  - Rockwell Kent, Blackhead Monhegan, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 44)
  - Rockwell Kent, Snow Fields..., 1909, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 45)
  - Rockwell Kent, Toilers on the Sea, 1907, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 46)
  - Edward Hopper, Hills South Truro, 1930, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 47)
  - Marsden Hartley, Spent Wave, 1937-8, 1937-1938; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 48)
  - Wyeth, Portrait of Young Artist, 1930, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 49)
  - Robert Henri, Rolling Sea, 1903, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 50)
  - Robert Henri, Storm Tide, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 51)
  - Leon Kroll, Monhegan Landscape, 1913, Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 52)
  - Winslow Homer -- Glossies, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 53)
  - Winslow Homer --- Transparencies, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 54)
  - Tony Cragg - slides, glossies, internegs, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 55)
  - Robert Morris Negs., Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 56)
  - Robert Morris Glossies, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 57)
  - Haden Whistler Pennell - Slides, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 58)
  - 10+10 Originals slides, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 59)
  - 10+10 Negatives, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 60)
  - 10+10+ originals glossies, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 70, Folder 61)
  - Black and White Glossies: Barye, Circa 1989-1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Photo Labels Barye, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Braque, Vanitas I 1938, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Degas, Femme Se Coifaant, 1881, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Degas, Ballet School, 1973, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Degas, Cabaret, 1882, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Picasso, Cafe De La Rotunde, 1901, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Monet, Willows at Vetheuil, 1880, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Labels For Glossies, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Original Glossies, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Japanese Camerra Pictorialists of California, 1929, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Itani Eel Fisherman, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Yaginuma Untitled (Boats), Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Itani The Curve, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Kunishige Aida Kawakami, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Robert Adams - B, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Robert Adams Photos, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Robert Adams Missouri River, Clay County, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Robert Adams/1977 Summer Nights, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Robert Adams / Perfect Times, Places, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Robert Adams / Catholic Church, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Robert Adams / Near Pendleton, Oregon, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Robert Adams / Summer Nights, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Robert Adams Ranch Yard, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Robert Adams Colorado Springs, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Robert Adams Cheyenne Mountain, Colorado, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Robert Adams Jefferson County, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Robert Adams on the Pidgeon Pass Road, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Robert Adams From Signal Hill, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - Robert Adams Nebraska State Highway 2, 1977-1978; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - [Three Master Printmakers - Press Kits], 1990 August 1; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Homeless in America, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - Spectrum: Ross and Willis, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  - Spectrum: Future of Photography, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 34)
  - Richard Pare-Fall, 1987; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  - Boutet De Monvel, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  - A Day in the Life of the Soviet Union, 1987; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 37)
  - Transco Watercolors +, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Views and Visions American Landscape Slides, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - [Loose Slides], Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - J.B. Murry Untitled, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - Michael Northuis Between Summits III, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - Steve Sweets New Orleans, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - Michael Northuis: Between Summits III 1988, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - Cheryl Goldsleger Scale: Central Passage, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Art Rosenbaum Wind Water, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Russ Warren Burial at Barrio San Antonio, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - Robert Warrens Fireworks II, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 48)
  - Antoine - Louis Barye Theseus Fighting a Centaur, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 49)
  - Corcoran Gallery - Photos, Slides and Prints, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Mapplethorpe Slides and Negatives, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 51)
  - Arena Glossies - Buried Child, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 52)
  - Arena Glossies - Enrico IV, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  - Arena Glossies - Waiting for Godot, Circa 1990 [August 17]; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 54)
  - Black Photographers Photos, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 55)
  - David Levinthal, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 56)
  - Cinidy Sherman #152, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 57)
  - Cindy Sherman #168, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 58)
  - Laurie Simmons, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 59)
  - Jean Cocteau, 1944, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 60)
  - Freed Dachau Prisoners Scavenging in the Rubbish Dump, 1945, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 61)
  - William Eggleston Color Transparencies, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 62)
  - Joseph Cornell Lee Miller (cont'd), Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 63)
  - Norman Field Hospital, Circa 1990; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 64)
  - U.S. Bomb Exploding of the Fortress of St. Malo, France, 1944, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 65)
  - Marlene Dietrich in Paris with the U.S.O to Entertain the troops, 1944, Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 66)
  - Worthington Whittredge - Press Kit, 1990 August 2; Series 11 (Box 71, Folder 67)
  - I Dream A World --- Negatives, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Ernestine Anderson, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Janet Collins, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Gwendolyn Brooks, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - I Dream A World - Slides, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Mayor Unita Blackwell, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Dr. Alexa Canady, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Maya Angelou, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Alice Walker, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Septima Poinsette Clark, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Josephine Matthews, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Johnnetta B. Cole, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Angela Davis, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Katherine Dunham, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Marian Wright Edelman, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Cora Leee Johnson, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Barbara Jordan, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Althea Gibson, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Rosa Parks, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Leontyne Price, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Wiilma Rudolph, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Priscilla Williams, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Carrie Saxon Perry, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Lena Horne, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Golub, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Diane Arbus: Magazine Work, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - My School III, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Spectrum Series: Natural Settings, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Spectrum Series: The Generic Figure, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Spectrum Series: In Other Words, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Articles Related to the Spectrum Series, Circa 1987-1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Black Image in American Art, 1989 September - 1990 February; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Black Image in American Art, 1990 March - September 1990; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Black Image in American Art, 1990 July - 1992 September; Series 11 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Ken Aptekar Press Release, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Ken Aptekar Checklist, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Aptekar: Catalogue, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Ken Aptekar Background, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Ken Aptekar Clippings, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Ken Aptekar: Images, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - 1997 WPA Art Auction, Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - 1997 Art Auction: Checklist, Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Emile Benes Brzezinski: Images, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Emile Benes Brzezinski Press Release, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Emile Benes Brzezinski: Label/Wall Text, vCirca 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Emile Benes Brzezinski, 1997; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Emile Benes Brzezinski Press Clippings, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Gene Young Images, 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Gene Young Press Release, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Nancy Chunn: Label/Wall Text, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Nancy Chunn: Images, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Nancy Chunn: Press Clippings, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Burgess/Dreyfuss/Tipton Collaboration Press Clippings, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Burgess/Dreyfuss/Tipton Collaboration Press Release, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Burgess/Dreyfuss/Tipton Collaboration Images, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Ida Applebroog: Images, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Ida Applebroog: Checklist, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Ida Applebroog: Background, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Ida Applebroog: Press Clippings, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - WPA/C: Come Out and Play Background, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - WPA/C: Frieze Checklist, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - WPA/C: of these times, Circa 1997-1998; Series 11 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Jackie: Background, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Soul of Spain Background, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Alchemy: Press Release, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Alchemy: Checklist, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Alchemy: Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Alchemy: Press Clippings, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Alchemy: Background, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Rov DeCarava Clippings, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Slides Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Larrabee, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - 98 Corcoran Faculty Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Helen Frankenthaler Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Helen Frankenthaler Press Release, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Helen Frankenthaler Label/Wall Text, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Constance Stuart Larrabee Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Artsites '98, 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Artsites 98 Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Artsites 98: Background, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Artsites 98: Press Clippings, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - National Scholastic Exhibition 1998: Press Clippings, Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - National Scholastic Exhibition 1998: Press Release, Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - National Scholastic Exhibition 1998: Images, Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - National Scholastics, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - [1998 Scholastic Awards], Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Roy DeCarava Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - [Roy DeCarava Loose], Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - DeCarava Background, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Roy DeCarava Checklist, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Linked To Landscape Images, Circa 1998; Series 11 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Jewels of the Romanovs - Images, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Manuel Neri Background, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Manuel Neri Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Manuel Neri Press Release, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Manuel Neri from Laura, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - [Manuel Neri Folders x2], Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Manuel Neri Images, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Mark Bennett Images, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Mark Bennett Press Release, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Mark Bennett, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Mark Bennet Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Options 1997 Clippings, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Options 1997 Images, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Options 1997 Label Text, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Options 1997 Press Release, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Print Club Images, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Print Club Background, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Press Release: Scholastic Art + Writing Awards: Margie Oliver 1997, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - 1997 National Scholastic Images, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - 1997 National Scholastic Background, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - [Alliance for Young Artists Writers], Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - [Scholastic Art Writing Awards x3], 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - 1997 National Scholastic Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - CAVA Background, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - 1997 CAVA: Label/Wall Text, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - 1997 CAVA: Press Clippings, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - 1997 CAVA: Images, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - 1997 CAVA: Press Release, Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Nozkowski Press Release, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Nozkowski: Background, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Thomas Nozkowski, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Nozkowski: Press Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - David Levinthal: Images, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - David Levinthal: Press Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - David Levinthal: Background, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Corcoran Alumni Hemicycle Exhibition: Label/Wall Text, 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - Corcoran Alumni Hemicycle Exhibition: Background, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - Crossing Over/Changing Places: Press Release, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - Crossing Over/Changing Places: Press Clippings, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - Crossing Over/Changing Places: Background, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - Crossing Over/Changing Places: Checklist, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - Crossing Over/Changing Places: Images, Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - [Crossing Over/Changing Places], Circa 1997; Series 11 (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - LIichtenstein Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Lichtenstein Images, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Lichtenstein Press Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Lichtenstein Checklist, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Lichtenstein: A Sculpture Retrospective, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Lichtenstein Label/Wall Text, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - [Lichtenstein Checklist], Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Lichtenstein Background, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - [BMW Lichtenstein], Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Evan Summer Press Clippings, 1999; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Evan Summer Background, 1999; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Evan Summer Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Images - Evan Summer, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Evan Summer Checklist, 1999; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Evan Summer, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - [Fellowships in the Arts], Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - FIVA: Background, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - FIVA: Clippings (empty), Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - FIVA: Checklist, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - FIVA: Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - FIVA: Images, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Schmeisser: Checklist, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Schmeisser: Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Schmeissser: Background, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Schmeisser: Images, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Elaine Kurtz Images, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Elaine Kurtz Background, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Elaine Kurtz Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Elaine Kurtz Press Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - Elaine Kurtz Checklist, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Elaine Kurtz Press Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - [Elaine Kurtz Packets], Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - Jacob Kainen Images, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - [Jacob Kainen Press Kits], Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - WPA/C Options 99 Release, 1999; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - WPA/C Options 99 Press Clippings, 1999; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - WPA/C Options 99 Images, 1999; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 37)
  - Images, 1999; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - Paper, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - [Dennis Oppenheim Press Kits], Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - [Dennis Oppenheim Press], Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 41)
  - Dennis Oppenheim Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 97, Folder 42)
  - To Conserve A Legacy Background, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - To Conserve A Legacy Label/Wall Text, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - To Conserve A Legacy Press Release, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - To Conserve A Legacy Checklist, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - To Conserve A Legacy info., Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - To Conserve A Legacy Press Kit, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Conserve A Legacy Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Conserve A Legacy Clippings, Circa 1999-2000; Series 11 (Box 99, Folder 8)